Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1983-1993, I.; Cassette 1-390
  - Fernandez, Robert Katibo (1980), 1988-03-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 364 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 209 Side b)
    Duration: 07:23
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_209bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_209bsc.mp3
  - François, Jean Charles Remarques pertinentes sur les crustacees... (1982/86), 1988-03-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 365 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 210 Side a)
    Duration: 28:06
    Performers: Carol Plantamura, dancer/vocalist; Jean-Charles Francois, dancer/pianist
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_210aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_210asc.mp3
  - Teitelbaum, Richard Golemics (1988), 1988-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 366 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 4, Audiocassette 211 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 105, March 16, 1988, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 40:32
    Performers: George Lewis, trombone; Richard Teitelbaum, piano and electronics
    Not in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_211aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_211asc.mp3
  - Bartlett, Martin, 1939-1993 Etats (1987), 1988-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 367 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 4, Audiocassette 211 Side b)
    Duration: 15:13
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_211bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_211bsc.mp3
  - Laske, Otto E. (Otto Ernst), 1936- Soliloquy (1984), 1988-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 368 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 212 Side a)
    Duration: 11:39
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_212aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_212asc.mp3
  - Truax, Barry Tongues of angels (1988), 1988-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 369 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 212 Side b)
    Performers: Lawrence Cherney, oboe/oboe d'amore/English horn
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_212bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_212bsc.mp3
  - Arcuri, Serge, 1954- Chronaxie (1984), 1988-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 370 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 213 Side a)
    Performers: Kirk Brundage, percussion
    Not in same order as printed program; Side b is blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_213aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_213asc.mp3
  - Felder, David, 1953- BoxMan (1987), 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 371 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 214 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 106, March 17, 1988, 8:00 p.m.
    Performers: Miles Anderson, trombone; Peter Weibel, video artist; Henry Jesionka, camera and video editing
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_214aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_214asc.mp3
  - Weidenaar, Reynold, 1945- Thundering scream of the seraphim's delight (1987), 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 372 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 214 Side b)
    Duration: 15:34
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_214bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_214bsc.mp3
  - Gibson, Jon Song I, string quartet (1974), 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 373 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 215 Side a)
    Performers: Unidentified strings performers
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_215aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_215asc.mp3
  - Gibson, Jon Interval (30.9 A) (1987), 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 374 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 215 Side b)
    Performers: Video
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_215bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_215bsc.mp3
  - Barlow, Klarenz, 1945- Fruitti d'amore (1988). Part 1, 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 375 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 216 Side a)
    Duration: 19:50
    World premiere; Not in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_216aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_216asc.mp3
  - Barlow, Klarenz, 1945- Fruitti d'amore (1988). Part 2, 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 375 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 216 Side b)
    Duration: 16:59
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_216bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_216bsc.mp3
  - Gibson, Jon Compositions, 1988-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 376 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 217 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 107, March 17, 1988, 11:00 p.m.
    Duration: 25:44
    Performers: Jon Gibson, soprano saxophone/flute, tape
    Studio Arena Stage Left Lounge (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    Five compositions performed without break: One, two, three; Rainforest, for tape and flute; Untitled; Extensions, for tape and saxophone; Song III; Side b is blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_217aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_217asc.mp3
  - Kagel, Mauricio Match (1964), 1988-03-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 377 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 218 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 108, March 18, 1988, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 19:31
    Performers: Frances-Marie Uitti, David Sims, violoncello; Jan Williams, percussion
    Tralfamadore Café (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_218aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_218asc.mp3
  - Kagel, Mauricio Presentation (1975), 1988-03-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 378 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 218 Side b)
    Duration: 21:33
    Performers: Paul Schmidt, actor; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_218bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_218bsc.mp3
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Pianobar pour Phaedre (1980), 1988-03-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 379 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 4, Audiocassette 219 Side a)
    Duration: 37:58
    Performers: Pauline Vaillancourt, soprano; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_219aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_219asc.mp3
  - Neill, Ben Money talk (1987), 1988-03-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 380 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 220 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 109, March 18, 1988, 11:00 p.m.
    Duration: 23:56
    Performers: Ben Neill, mutantrumpet; Don Yallech, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_220aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_220asc.mp3
  - Neill, Ben Dis-solution 2 (1986), 1988-03-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 381 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 220 Side b)
    Duration: 10:49
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_220bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_220bsc.mp3
  - Neill, Ben No more people (1988), 1988-03-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 382 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 221 Side a)
    Duration: 12:47
    Performers: Dora Ohrenstein, soprano; Ben Neill, mutantrumpet; Don Yallech, percussion; Gregory Piontek, violoncello
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_221aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_221asc.mp3
  - Corner, Philip, 1933- Gamelan adagio (1987), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 383 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 222 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 110, March 19, 1988, 2:30 p.m.
    Duration: 11:57
    Performers: Gamelan Son of Lion
    Lancaster Opera House
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_222aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_222asc.mp3
  - Benary, Barbara Plainsong (1987), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 384 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 222 Side b)
    Duration: 10:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_222bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_222bsc.mp3
  - Liben, Lauren Traffic (1984), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 385 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 223 Side a)
    Duration: 09:15
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_223aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_223asc.mp3
  - Goode, Daniel Welcome slendro clarinet (1986), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 386 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 223 Side b)
    Duration: 12:42
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_223bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_223bsc.mp3
  - Gamelan Son of Lion Collective Chuck, 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 387 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 224 Side a)
    Duration: 06:36
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_224aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_224asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Concerto for piano with Javanese gamelan. Bull's belle., 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 388 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 224 Side b)
    Duration: 15:36
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_224bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_224bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Coyote stories with shadow puppets, 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 389 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 225 Side a)
    Duration: 16:26
    Performers: Carl Johengen, voice; Gamelan Son of Lion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_225aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_225asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Fifth simfony (1939), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 390 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 226 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 111, March 19, 1988, 8:00 p.m.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_226aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_226asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Ariadne (1987), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 391 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 226 Side b)
    Duration: 07:38
    Performers: Ann LaBerge, flute; Robert Fernandez, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_226bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_226bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Summerfield set (1988), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 392 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 227 Side a)
    Duration: 13:01
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_227aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_227asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Labyrinth no. 3 (1940-41), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 393 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 227 Side b)
    Duration: 20:35
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_227bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_227bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Concerto, organ (1973), 1988-03-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 394 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 228 Side a)
    Duration: 28:34
    Performers: James Bigham, organ; UB Percussion Ensemble; Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_228aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_228asc.mp3
  - Crumb, George Zeitgeist (1988), 1989-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 395 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 5, Audiocassette 229 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 112, April 11, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 35:10
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_229aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_229asc.mp3
  - Crumb, George Ancient voices of children (1970), 1989-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 396 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 5, Audiocassette 229 Side b)
    Duration: 28:12
    Performers: Chamber Concerts Canada Ensemble
    World premiere of choreography by David Earle
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_229bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_229bsc.mp3
  - Torke, Michael Yellow pages (1985), 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 397 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 230 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 113, April 12, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 07:04
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_230aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_230asc.mp3
  - Carter, Elliott, 1908-2012 Enchanted preludes (1987), 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 398 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 230 Side b)
    Duration: 05:46
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_230bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_230bsc.mp3
  - Boulez, Pierre, 1925-2016 Derive (1982), 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 399 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 231 Side a)
    Duration: 07:29
    One of the composer's Spots.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_231aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_231asc.mp3
  - Lang, David (David A.) Illumination rounds (1986), 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 400 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 231 Side b)
    Duration: 11:41
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_231bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_231bsc.mp3
  - Fernandez, Robert Tentacles (1987), 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 401 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 232 Side a)
    Duration: 06:56
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_232aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_232asc.mp3
  - Jarvinen, Arthur Seven golden vampires (1986), 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 402 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 232 Side b)
    Duration: 10:52
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_232bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_232bsc.mp3
  - Steiger, Rand, 1957- 13 loops, 1989-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 403 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 233 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_233aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_233asc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic Spots. Turtle and the crane (1987), 1989-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 404 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 234 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 114, April 13, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 25:09
    Performers: Aki Takahashi, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_234aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_234asc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic Spots. Mary's dream, 1989-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 405 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 234 Side b)
    Duration: 19:30
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_234bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_234bsc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic Spots. Mayn yingele (1989), 1989-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 406 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 235 Side a)
    Duration: 26:16
    Performers: Frederic Rzewski, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_235aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_235asc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic Coming together (1969), 1989-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 407 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 235 Side b)
    Duration: 20:14
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_235bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_235bsc.mp3
  - Daugherty, Michael, 1954- Phantom of the opera. Part 1, 1989-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 408 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 5, Audiocassette 236 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 120, April 15, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 47:23
    Performers: Michael Daugherty, synthesizer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_236aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_236asc.mp3
  - Daugherty, Michael, 1954- Phantom of the opera. Part 2, 1989-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 408 Tape type: TDK_SA-100 (Box 5, Audiocassette 236 Side b)
    Duration: 34:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_236bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_236bsc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Wayang IV (1981), 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 409 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 237 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 122, April 16, 1989, 2:00 p.m.
    Performers: Anthony Davis, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_237aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_237asc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Lady of the mirrors (1979), 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 410 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 237 Side b)
    Duration: 07:32
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_237bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_237bsc.mp3
  - Monk, Thelonious Crepuscule with Nellie, 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 411 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 238 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_238aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_238asc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Five moods from an English garden (1979), 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 412 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 238 Side b)
    Duration: 12:23
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_238bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_238bsc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Behind the rock, 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 413 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 239 Side a)
    Duration: 07:33
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_239aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_239asc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Middle passage, 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 414 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 239 Side b)
    Duration: 13:09
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_239bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_239bsc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Walk through the shadow (1979), 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 415 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 240 Side a)
    Duration: 09:25
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_240aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_240asc.mp3
  - Monk, Thelonious Evidence, 1989-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 416 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 240 Side b)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 123, April 16, 1989, 5:00 p.m.
    Duration: 04:33
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_240bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_240bsc.mp3
  - Smetanin, Michael Ladder of escape (1984), 1989-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 417 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 241 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 126, April 17, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 03:53
    Performers: Terra Australis
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_241aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_241asc.mp3
  - Kriesberg, Matthias Imaginary themes (1988), 1989-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 418 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 241 Side b)
    Duration: 20:52
    Performers: Scott Tinney, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_241bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_241bsc.mp3
  - Hyla, Lee, 1952-2014 Dream of innocent !II (1987), 1989-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 419 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 242 Side a)
    Duration: 17:54
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_242aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_242asc.mp3
  - Formosa, Riccardo, 1954- Domino (1983), 1989-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 420 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 242 Side b)
    Duration: 06:03
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_242bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_242bsc.mp3
  - Martino, Donald, 1931-2005 Parisonatina al'dodecaphonia (1963), 1989-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 421 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 243 Side a)
    Duration: 10:28
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_243aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_243asc.mp3
  - Ince, Kamran Kac (1983), 1989-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 422 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 243 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_243bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_243bsc.mp3
  - Ichiyanagi, Toshi, 1933- Piano media (1972), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 423 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 244 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 127, April 18, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 07:20
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_244aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_244asc.mp3
  - Takemitsu, Tōru For away (1973), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 424 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 244 Side b)
    Duration: 06:54
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_244bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_244bsc.mp3
  - Takemitsu, Tōru Rain tree sketch (1982), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 425 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 245 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_245aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_245asc.mp3
  - Garland, Peter, 1952- Jornada del muerto (1987), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 426 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 245 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_245bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_245bsc.mp3
  - Boulez, Pierre, 1925-2016 Douze notations (1948), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 427 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 246 Side a)
    Duration: 10:40
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_246aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_246asc.mp3
  - Scelsi, Giacinto, 1905-1988 Cinque incantesimi (1953), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 428 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 246 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_246bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_246bsc.mp3
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Extensions III (1952), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 429 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 247 Side a)
    Duration: 07:43
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_247aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_247asc.mp3
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001 Herma (1961), 1989-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 430 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 247 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_247bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_247bsc.mp3
  - Chadabe, Joel After some songs. Part 1, 1989-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 431 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 5, Audiocassette 248 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 128, April 19, 1989, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 25:38
    Performers: Jan Williams, percussion; Joel Chadabe, computer/synthesizer
    Stated in program as Twenty-four go, a world premiere. Introduced as After some songs